Jesse Stone: Sea Change is a drama, crime, tv
movie film directed by Robert Harmon.
Police Chief Jesse Stone's relationship with his ex-wife
worsens, and he fears he's relapsing into alcoholism.
To get his mind off his problems, Jesse begins working on the
unsolved murder of a bank teller shot during a robbery.
Also, his investigation of an alleged rape draws him into conflict with the town council —
which hopes to preserve Paradise's reputation as an ideal seaside resort.
Jesse Stone, played by Tom Selleck.
Rose Gammon, played by Kathy Baker.
Luther 'Suitcase' Simpson, played by Kohl Sudduth.
Leeann Lewis, played by Rebecca Pidgeon.
Sybil Martin, played by Sean Young.
Cathleen Holton, played by Mika Boorem.
Jesse Stone: Sea Change is a 2007 American made-for-television crime drama film directed
by Robert Harmon and starring Tom Selleck, Kathy Baker, and Kohl Sudduth.
Based on the 2006 novel Sea Change by Robert B.
Parker, the film is about Jesse Stone, the police chief of a small New England town who investigates the unsolved murder of Rebecca Lewis, a bank teller shot during a
robbery, and an alleged rape that draws him into conflict with the town council who hope to preserve the town's reputation as an ideal seaside resort.
Filmed on location in Nova Scotia, the story is set in the
fictitious town of Paradise, Massachusetts.
Jesse Stone: Sea Change is the fourth in a series of nine
television films based on Parker's Jesse Stone novels.
The fourth film in the series, it first aired on the
CBS television network March 22, 2007.
Selleck was nominated for a Primetime Emmy Award for Outstanding Lead Actor in a Miniseries
or Movie for his performance in the film at the 59th Primetime Emmy Awards.
Cinematographer Rene Ohashi was nominated for an American Society of Cinematographers Award for Outstanding Achievement in Cinematography
in Motion Picture, Limited Series, or Pilot Made for Television at the 2007 American Society of Cinematographers Awards.
The tone is emotional and intense.